-[insects chirping]
-[rumbling]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
[thudding]
[roars, screeches]
[grunts, pants]
[fly buzzing]
[all panting]
[shudders, sighs]
Oh...
Okay...
-[screams]
-[all scream]
[sighs] Sorry, I stepped on a twig.
-Ugh, come on, man.
-You done gave me a heart attack!
-I should step on you.
-It's okay, Ben.
-We're all on edge.
-And lost.
Yeah, we've been out here for a while now.
Darius, we sure we're still headed
towards the park?
Well, we'd be sure
if I still had my phone,
because it has a GPS, a compass app,
and is also a phone!
Sammy didn't steal your phone!
No one stole your phone!
Can we please stop talking
about the phone?
You guys! You guys, you guys, you guys.
Could you all yell at each other
quieter, please?
My fellow campers, chill!
What we need here is someone who can
make the hard call on what to do next.
Since I'm obviously leadership material...
I'll do this.
And my first decree as leader is
for everyone to stop talking
and just listen to Darius.
-Huh?
-You got us out of camp alive.
Plus, I can blame you
if anybody gets eaten.
Leadership. [chuckles]
So, which way, Darius?
Please, you're just trying to cover up
the fact that you're lost, too, Mr. VIP.
-None of us know where we are.
-I know where we are!
We're by the Carnotaurus paddock!
I thought this place looked familiar.
Am I an excellent leader or what?
I remember the fence.
-The broken, ripped-down fence.
-[Ben panting]
That means... That means Toro
is out here... with us.
Now we have to deal
with the Indominus and Toro.
Hold up. How do you know about Toro?
We all know. Kenji told us, like,
the day after it happened.
In my defense,
me saving you was super cool.
[sighs]
We know this enclosure
is due north of the main park.
So, if we keep going that way,
we'll hit the visitors' center.
We're sure to find Dave and Roxie,
or someone else there in charge.
Yes! Exactly what I was thinking,
as leader, which I am.
Follow me!
I don't think finding an adult
is going to help.
A terrifying, camouflaged dinosaur
trashed our camp.
No way they have a plan for that.
Ben, I know it's scary,
but this is Jurassic World.
Dealing with dinosaurs is what they do.
They didn't deal so well
back at their first park, did they? Hmm?
Everything will be okay. Trust me.
[rumbling]
[growling]
[Roxie] Ugh! This is taking forever!
I know Claire's a busy lady,
but we can't leave the kids alone all day.
Wow, hittin' the first names.
You only do that when you're annoyed.
Of course I'm annoyed, David.
We need to talk to Claire
and get back to the kids ASAP!
But instead, they shove us in here
and just tell us to wait for her,
and then everyone just disappears!
Where'd they go?
Something's going on.
Look, I'm sure Claire--
yeah, that's not gonna work--
Ms. Dearing will get to us when she can.
When? We've been here so long,
someone gave you a birthday card to sign.
All right, the real issue
is that no one else signed it.
That's just sad. Poor... Eddie.
"Dear Eddie,
I don't know you,
but I'm sure you're doing..."
Will you put that down
and help me find a phone or radio?
We have to get ahold of someone,
ideally, Claire Dearing.
Okay, maybe she's hiding so she doesn't
have to sign this card and--
-Are you picking that lock?
-What?
I watched Brooklynn's
"Hacks for When You Lock Yourself
Out of Your Hotel Room" video.
It was actually so good, I subscribed.
Don't tell her.
-Almost.
-[lock clicks]
Ugh, I'm so good.
Mildly impressive.
[screaming over radios]
-[man 1] Shoot her!
-[screaming continues]
Shoot her!
-[man 2] No! The order is to get--
-[man 3] Save Wu!
-Keep out of the way!
-[velociraptors screeching]
[static crackles]
[birds chirping]
[Sammy grunts]
Don't let Brooklynn upset you.
She's just being... Brooklynn.
Yaz, there's something I... [gasps]
[Sammy] The Indominus rex was here.
[Darius] Predators don't kill prey
and then just leave without feeding.
This... this isn't right.
-[low groaning]
-[all gasp]
[all scream, pant]
[Ben screams, pants]
[whimpers]
[rustling]
-[snarls]
-[all scream]
[soft growling]
Bumpy!
[chuckles]
And drooly, and smelly.
How do you even know
that's the same dinosaur?
Her big head bump.
Dr. Wu said she's asymmetrical,
but he's wrong that it's bad.
And so what if she is asymmetrical?
There's nothing wrong
with being different, or bumpy,
or getting tired after reading
an overly thrilling book!
And maybe if her parents
had listened to her,
she wouldn't have come here
and gotten attacked!
Are we still talking about the dinosaur?
Feels like we're not still talking
about the dinosaur.
As fun as this reunion is,
shouldn't we keep moving south?
I'm not spending another hour
walking through the jungle,
hoping that we don't
run into that Indominus.
We need a new plan.
Uh, yeah, obviously we need a new plan.
So, I had Darius figure out a new one.
Lay it on us, bro.
Okay.
So, uh... we need to find
somewhere safe close by.
If camp is that way,
and the park is that way...
[gasps] Isn't Dr. Wu's field genetics lab
near here?
You guys went on the tour.
Does this area look familiar?
Um... Yeah. Y-Yeah.
-I think it might be over that way.
-That seems right.
Great! That's where we should go.
There's bound to be an adult there
who can help or tell us what to do.
Right?
-[faint roaring]
-[all gasp]
Fine, whatever! Let's just go to the lab.
As long as we are moving away from that.
[soft growling]
What about Bumpy?
She's a dinosaur, bro.
She belongs out here in the wild.
And she'll just slow us down.
We gotta go now.
[soft growling]
Ugh! [grunts]
We're doing the right thing, yeah?
Going towards the genetics lab?
Or should we have stayed at camp?
Would that have been safer?
How are you so calm about this?
I told you, if someone gets eaten,
I'm not to blame, you are.
Lea-der-ship.
But if I'm leading us the wrong way,
the person getting eaten could be you.
Are you sure
we should be going to the lab?
[screams]
Why are we moving so slowly?
Let's pick it up, people.
Wait.
Guys, where's Ben?
[grunting]
-[soft growling]
-Shh! Shh!
-Come on. Oh!
-[Yasmina clears throat]
Hey!
How's it hangin'... dudes?
Ben, are you hiding Bumpy in that bush?
[soft bellowing]
Nope. That could be anything.
The jungle makes
all sorts of weird noises.
-[soft growling]
-[grunts]
How did she get here?
We don't have time for this!
There are dinosaurs eating people
out here, and Bumpy can't keep up!
She can move faster.
Ankylosauruses run fast. Right, Darius?
When they're fully grown, maybe,
but she's just...
[snoring]
Wow! Yeah, total speed demon.
Say goodbye, Ben.
[groans]
No!
You say hello,
because she is coming with us!
So... there!
Ben, you're not thinking this through.
Bumpy's too slow.
Then... then we'll put her in the van!
[scoffs] What van?
That one!
It's an ACU transport!
Asset containment unit.
Got the tour of their HQ.
Super hardcore dino-trapping
security dudes.
Then where are they?
-Is that a tablet? [grunts]
-[Darius grunts]
[sighs] What did they tell us?
Oh, right. Come on, channel six.
Dave, Roxie! Can y'all hear us?
[static crackles]
And of course this doesn't have
communication enabled.
Because you know what?
Why would it?
If I had my phone--
Enough already!
There are bigger things
going on here than your phone!
[tablet beeping]
There's a map program
with little moving dots on it.
[Darius] They chip all the dinosaurs
electronically to track them.
See? There's us, and there's...
Wait. Here's the Brachiosaurus Grove
on the map,
so why are the Brachiosauruses
way over there?
I think maybe the fences are down.
-At least some of them.
-[Bumpy growls]
[squealing]
[pants] Easy, girl.
[rumbling]
-[Bumpy whines]
-[Ben] Guys?
Something's coming this way.
That's weird.
Whatever that is,
it isn't showing up on the tablet.
What kind of dinosaur
wouldn't have a transponder?
I am not in the mood to find out.
-[Bumpy squealing]
-[Ben] Shh! Shh!
-Ben, shut her up!
-[roaring]
[screams] We gotta go now!
-[Brooklynn] Go! Go!
-[Darius] Move!
Wait! Doesn't anyone know
how to drive a van?
No, but we drove gyrospheres, right?
It can't be that different.
The gyrospheres had joysticks
and a Jimmy Fallon tutorial.
-I don't even have my learners permit!
-I do!
[grunts]
-Hands at ten and two--
-Kenji, go, quickly!
-[tires screech]
-[all scream]
[Ben] Wrong way! Wrong way!
-[Kenji grunts]
-[tires screech]
[roaring]
[roars]
It's gaining! Go faster!
-I can't!
-You're in the wrong gear!
-Well, how do I shift gears?
-How should I know?
[bellowing]
[all scream]
[roars]
-It's coming!
-Step on that thing!
-Zigzag!
-Are you signaling?
Can everyone not yell at me
while I'm saving our lives?
[roars]
Drive!
[all screaming]
[Brooklynn] No!
[roars]
[all scream]
[all grunt, pant]
At least we lost Indominus.
-Now... where do we go?
-[Bumpy groans]
How about into the genetics lab?
It's a gift.
[doors hiss]
What?
-[grunts]
-[all scream]
[screaming]
[sighs] Not dinosaurs.
You're not dinosaurs.
[sighs] This is the worst birthday ever.
Again, we are so happy we found you.
Things are crazy!
There's a giant camouflaged dinosaur
out there.
Also, regular dinosaurs.
We've been hoping to find someone--
You're sure you closed the door
behind you, right?
Uh...
I think so.
-You think, or you know?
-[Kenji belches]
Sorry?
Did you want it back?
You know what? Doesn't matter.
The dinosaurs got out and no one
bothered to tell me; they just ran.
So, why not? Knock yourself out.
Ugh! There's no dial tone!
The landlines are down.
So is the radio, and cell phone service
keeps cutting out.
But the park obviously has a plan.
So, what's that plan? What do we do?
You're asking me? [laughs]
Asking me?
Is that, like, a good freaky laugh?
Do you not get it? We're doomed.
No one is coming to help!
But what about Dr. Wu, or--
Wu? Who do you think is to blame?
Wu got greedy.
And instead of dinosaurs,
he built monsters!
[whirring]
Masrani, Dearing,
they're all clueless
about what's really going on here.
And after everything I did
for the other guys--
Other guys? What other--
It doesn't matter, does it?
Jurassic World isn't a park.
It's a powder keg,
and it is detonating all around us!
We're all going down.
End of story!
No, you have to know what to do.
You're an adult!
Don't look at me.
I was just hiding until you all barged in.
But we drove all the way here 'cause--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-You have a vehicle?
-[grunts]
Guys, I left the keys in the van.
Stop! What are you doing?
Getting out of here alive!
[panting]
-[grunts]
-[squeals]
[grunts]
Ow!
[squeals]
Bumpy! [pants]
-Huh? [pants]
-[engine starts]
-[engine revs]
-[Yasmina yelps]
[grunts]
-[roars]
-[all scream]
[roars]
[pants] Ah! [grunts]
-[growls]
-[yelps]
[screams]
Oh, no! [whimpers]
[screams, whimpers]
-[pants]
-[metal creaks]
-[roars]
-[Eddie screams]
-[Sammy whimpers]
-[all panting]
-[Kenji] What?
-[Darius] Come on, are you kidding me?
Perfect! The park's only intact fence!
-[roaring]
-[all scream, pant]
I told you she'd get in the way!
If it wasn't for her,
I could have made the van.
And then you would have been eaten.
Bumpy saved your life.
Why couldn't you just leave her behind?
Because I won't abandon her like we were!
[low groaning]
Ben's right.
We're on our own.
-[roaring]
-[all scream]
[rumbling]
[panting]
[snarling]
[squeals]
-[Ben gasps]
-[Bumpy growls]
[snarls]
[shushing]
[growling]
[gasps]
[whispers] Trust me.
[roars]
[growling]
[clanging]
[roars]
[Ben and Kenji panting]
-[grunts, gasps]
-[tablet trilling]
-[roars]
-[whimpers]
-[all scream]
-Brooklynn!
[whimpers]
-[both scream]
-[snarls]
[both yelp]
-[screaming, panting]
-[rhythmic clanging]
Hey, over here!
[roars]
-[Darius] Whoa! [pants]
-[roars]
-[Sammy whimpering]
-[Bumpy squeals]
I'm driving.
[engine starts]
Wait! Where's Darius?
-[roaring]
-[panting, whimpering]
Whoa!
-[screams]
-[snarling]
[panting]
[Darius yelps]
[roaring]
Whew! [pants, chuckles]
-[all laughing]
-[Bumpy squeals]
Yeah!
[Roxie over radio] Kids?
Come on, pick up!
There's something going on.
Stay at camp.
-We're heading to you.
-[static crackles]
[Darius] No, we're heading to you!
Darius! Wait, why are you--
We're fine, but we had to leave camp.
-What?
Long story.
[Yasmina] Short story:
a dinosaur ate camp.
[Kenji] Shorter story: epic leader Kenji
somehow got everyone out safely.
[Ben] And then we found a van and Bumpy!
[Bumpy squeals]
I got nothing.
[Darius] We're cutting through the jungle
and heading to the main park.
Should be there soon.
-We're getting out of here!
-[cheering]
-Yeah! You hear that, Bumpy?
-Whoo! Driver en route.
[Kenji sighs]
Good job not getting me eaten, bro.
Thanks, "brah."
Oh, no, you-- you made that sound weird.
No more bro-talk for you.
[laughs]
We did it, camp family!
-And not a moment too--
-[all grunt]
[grunting continues]
[Brooklynn] My phone.
I knew it!
-[gasps]
-[Yasmina] Huh?
Sammy?
-[crashing]
-[all screaming]
[theme music playing]